Would be great to start from MOVE-X,
then look at the XML and on the other
side look at the PAS-X side.
OK.
OK.
So I'll start up MOVE-X here. I'll,
need some help from Anu and Jorgen.
See,
because when we when we did the mapping
it was we.
We were unsure about a few rows of what
exactly they meant or where they
originated or things like this,
so it's not a perfect document yet.
OK, no problem, we can shape it up. It's.
Think.
OK.
So we used the article 230119.
And this is a bulk,
so it's not a finished product used,
but maybe we'll we'll have to do that in
the future.
Maybe we'll start with a non finished
product and then go for a packaging order
or something like that.
See the difference?
OK, Max,
where can I see the article number here
on this screen?
Uh, no way. Yet,
this is just a starting uh menu. So.
OK.
Let's see.
We can find a.
Maybe I should look in PAS-X first to
just see if we can find an order to
follow it all the way.
So give me a second.
Can't you use the one we had on the XML?
But wasn't that aborted? I've.
Ohh, it may be worse. Ah.
Yeah, it was. You're right.
Yeah, but, but, but for our task,
I think it it didn't mean it didn't
No, no. Yeah, correct.
matter so.
It's gonna take something that is
finished.
OK.
OK, so let's see,
we want to check the batch itself.
We want to check the article specific
data, the article type data.
And the production line data and then the,
uh, BOM itself.
Umm.
Yes.
So Jorgen,
you said when it pulls data from the
batch it pulls it from PMS 001.
I think last time.
But that's that's when the when it's
created, right?
I think we.
Yeah, that means PMS100.
Basically, yeah. Yeah, exactly. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is the overview,
which you can go in afterwards and then
check. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, yes, yes, exactly.
And So what we bring from here should be.
The manufacturing order number.
Up here.
Uh.
The product number, right,
it's coming from here.
The material. Yeah. Yeah.
The material number products number, yeah.
And there a reference order number I
think, correct.
At.
Get the batch number right.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. What?
What do you see it? Ohh there. There.
Yeah. The batch number. Yeah. Yeah.
Uh to the right. Yeah, right. Yeah.
Batch, batch, batch.
We also have the timestamp.
See.
Yeah, the created date right?
Because you have a planned date and a
planned time as well,
but I don't really see it in here.
We got the actual dates.
This planned planned is start date and
finish date.
And the actual values and this is real
Ohh ohh here.
Ohh. OK OK. Yeah. Yeah.
So this is the planned one. Yeah. OK. OK.
Yes.
But.
Yeah.
Just gonna scroll through and see if we
pick up any and other data from the batch.
Don't think we do in in this right?
We don't have the order quantity.
Ohh, right, right, right target material.
And It's basically this,
so I'm not entirely sure where it picks
it up. If it's from the BOM,
or if it's from.
I think that's coming from this the order,
the product number
OK.
The product number, yeah.
So target material and target quantity,
how much we've ordered is.
Yeah, on the order.
They even want to you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
In the middle of the screen. Yeah. Yeah,
yeah, yeah.
Yeah,
I was looking for without apostrophe.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And you get the unit of measurement as
well.
Yeah.
And and also yeah,
if you change this it changes in here so
it can always pull this latest data from
PMS 100, right?
So if you were to do any changes,
you can just go back because it would
Yeah.
update in here as well.
Yes.
Yeah.
OK.
I I think that's it from from batch data
then.
Yep, it looks like it and that's.
Yeah. Should we?
Move on to.
This is when the batch is created right
at the first.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So we created them PMS 001 and then PMS
Yeah.
100 is where you can view it in
afterwards.
And this is the article specific data.
So you have all the these parameters.
And this were were the one.
It's this one is a little bit special
because depending on what type of batch
it is,
if it's like an experimental it should
send this value.
If it's a validation it's this value or
if it's production.
It's this value.
Umm.
And then basically.
The rest here is.
Parameters uh number parameter string
parameter boolean.
Which are used within the order to set up
different things.
Yeah, so these are.
boolean so.
They they probably have an the activate
or deactivate certain function in the
finished MBR.
And all the others are just giving values
in 2 different positions in activities or
functions.
Umm.
Should we take some screenshots there
maybe.
We Max,
we are recording the session so it's no
It would.
Ohh, right, right, right. Yeah. Yeah.
OK OK, yeah.
problem. Yeah. So we can take from there.
I have one small question here.
When you look at these parameters that
activate you know certain things in.
PAS-X system,
is there any documentation at all of how
the MBR is set up for a particular code?
Like in this case for this article number
and then what is the corresponding
Attributes or parameters that actually
influence them?
Is there any documentation as such?
I'm at the list.
It's. Yeah, it's not a.
An official document in and that.
And.
It's the PVL list.
That corresponds to this right for a
specific GMBR.
Yeah, I. Yeah. Yeah, sure. Yeah. Yeah,
I I guess you can call that uh
OK.
documentation as well, but yeah.
Yeah.
So I think we'll need that as well to
look at that.
So what we are showing right now,
we are clear that, OK,
this is material and you're showing me
some material specific parameters.
That influence PAS-X, so this is clear.
Yeah.
Yeah, uh. Oop then we have.
You know, we actually need to.
It's up, I guess.
Uh, this was for like 2.
So in the BOM,
There are references to
The different planning groups,
so this is the production type planning
group.
And these 2 are line specific.
So both of them are in the BOM,
but when we plan to one of the lines only
one. Yeah.
You send those parameters that are for
line this specific line.
OK.
And and this planning groups are nothing
but your resources or your machines?
Uh.
I mean, if you plan it to to line 2,
you get specific additional parameters or
they are set up just for line 2.
OK.
So they are.
Yeah, and the same for the product type.
And and these parameters are also. Sorry.
Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, no, no.
And the same goes for the article type
there.
So the that sets up or send specific
parameters for the the the product type.
OK, so in this case,
if we have the planning group here.
And let's say there are specific
parameters for line 2.
Are they also maintained in MOVE-X and
managed from MOVE-X?
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So MOVE-X is the master and PAS-X follows.
OK. Can can we go to that one?
So this is OK,
you're already showing the planning group.
Yeah. Yeah.
So there's a planning group and this is
for line 2 specific.
OK.
All the manufacturing land area.
Oops.
It is, yeah.
And these ones I'm gonna try to explain
it.
I'm not entirely sure we've discussed
this over and over.
Why these are needed but they are
referenced to how many basic operations
are linked or have a ERP position to them?
So for line 2 we have 7 basic operations
connected to with an ERP position.
And for line one, we only have 6,
so and I am a bit unsure why it's needed.
But we have it and it doesn't really work
without it.
OK.
So.
So these are number of operations on that
line.
Yeah,
that are linked with ERP position in that
are given unique ERP positions.
We can check look at those in the XML
later.
OK. Just just one question.
So if something is going on,
Hmm.
let's say there is,
I'm assuming that there are multiple
products on the same line too or its
product specific.
I.
There are different products in there,
yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We have around 800 SKU 's.
In the same.
On line 2?
Ohh no no.
No, no, no, not on line 2
So there could be multiple on line 2.
Yeah.
So,
so out of this 7 are all 7 operations
always executed for each of the material
that goes on the on line 2?
Yeah, yeah, yes.
Or this can be less, more or less?
No,
they are always always active for for
this.
OK, clear.
And we used the same GMBR for line 1.
But we turn off one of the work rooms,
which has the number 7. So,
One of the rooms, right? Yeah.
OK.
for line one we only have 6.
Here.
OK, understand.
And below are the parameters for this
line in the BOM
Yes,
and it's a lot of containers specific for
that line. The room parameters,
which rooms that differs from line one,
right?
So and then you have the Boolean is
active line one.
It's not true and then line one is true.
OK.
To activate and deactivate uh functions
in the in the process system to get
Yeah.
specific instructions for uh, line 2,
for instance, so on.
OK.
OK, fine.
And I have one very technical question,
but not sure who can help.
So every parameter what we saw was in
that table PXOPAR what?
I think Jorgen shared with us last week.
So are these parameters also in that same
exactly same table or there are multiple
tables like this?
Do we have any information on that?
I'm not sure exactly what table or Jorgen
if you have more information there.
I think we had.
I sent an extractor one table PX
something. Can't remember the name,
but I don't.
PXOPAR something?
Yeah. Yeah, exactly.
And and when I checked the PX files we
have.
And.
Well done.
Lots of PX files and we need to check the.
Uh.
You need to check the program to see
which ones it will use this because there
Yeah.
are lots of other PX files also related
to the PAS-X interface,
but not necessarily used by.
As as parameters because basically we
only have one table with with parameters.
OK.
So.
OK, no problem, Jorgen.
I don't want to divert.
Let's go with our flow.
Maybe I will connect to you after this
call and we can check if there are any
more tables that will have this
information. So I would.
Look at this specific material and see if
it whatever we are seeing for from the
line perspective etcetera are also
maintained in that table for this
particular planning group and the
material.
Yeah. Should we continue?
Yeah. Yes, Max. Sorry. Yep.
Yeah.
Whereas this is the product type specific.
So this is the soft and sweet products.
Um.
And this is still still the same,
uh article number.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But it's also connected to this uh
permetalist so.
There are multiple soft and sweet
products and these all share the these
settings,
so that's why they are gathered in in
this parameter list.
There's all of those articles that is put
down as soft and sweet. They will,
they will get information from this,
this group as well.
Yes. And then we have the BOM.
And we were a bit unsure of some data
where it's picked up and everything,
but we we have.
Let's see.
No,
we don't have the ERP position in here.
PDF.
No, you don't see it here.
OK,
maybe it's better to look in and do it on.
There we go.
It ohh it's OK. Yeah,
it just went right and.
Hmm.
OK. Yeah, so here it is.
And and this is the BOM used by MOVE-X.
So the BOM position.
Uh, you just move, move X and then.
OK.
PAS-X uses this.
So so this gets created, uh.
We have several rows of of the bill of
material in in the XML.
And these help to populate several of
those with the quantity or the material
number and everything like that.
How? How is this so? For example,
when you look at the BOM component
position versus the PAS-X position,
how are they mapped?
Like for example this 5 mapped to 009.
Yeah.
Is this mapping maintained somewhere in
the MOVE-X system?
Yes, we we maintain it right here.
In this page and it needs to be connected
with the GMBR.
OK,
so somebody has to manually enter 005 and
009 while the creation of the BOM.
No, it no, not really. But yeah, well,
Daniel, you go.
No. Go on on. Sorry.
No, no, it's it's, yeah,
so so this this column that Max is
showing now this is this come these are
the positions from these are the BOM
positions from the from the MOVE-X bill
of material and so the value that is
maintained here is the one.
In the next column where we have 009,
001 and so on.
So this is what Anu and I maintain for
each article.
So and this is what I what I mentioned.
I think in the last meeting that since we
were not consistent with the BOM
positions in the in the in the MOVE-X
BOMs.
We had to have this extra table here to
to be able to map with the with the ERP
positions in in PAS-X because they need
to match and since we were not consistent
it MOVE-X.
Here we for example,
we always have the gum base,
for example on the first row is always
position 009 for example.
It was not consistent in the in the
finished goods articles.
Yeah.
OK, so if I have to see this BOM in PAS-X,
I would see based on the position which
is this one.
Yeah, on the right here, PVL.
Yeah. Yeah. On the right. Yeah. Yeah.
So the rest of the information here is
Yeah.
OK, so so.
just picked up in this in this PXS 130.
This is picked up from from PDS 001,
from the BOM in MOVE-X.
OK, so so in PAS-X.
At.
And a sub program probably or a sub page
probably for for that, yeah.
OK,
so my question would be that when I look
at this PVL and the PAS-X positions,
do they get sorted out later on where
which for example 001 will be first, 002,
003 and so on, will it automatically?
Get the reshuffle as an ascending number
in PAS-X.
Hmm.
Not sure what you mean.
I mean they they will just go into
wherever we have said that they should be
so.
So we use these BOM ERP positions and and
use the material where we.
Yeah.
Is it? Is it possible?
So so it so in the GMBR, you know,
wherever you go.
This I mean when you you will reference
this material with BOM position 009 for
example.
Hmm.
So I don't know if it's if you know,
talking about sorting is is actually
relevant.
I mean in the in the PVL for the PAS-X,
they are of course sorted because they
are just, you know listed alphabetically,
but.
Uh.
Is that what is that your question?
Yeah.
I I I just wanted to know what happens to
this sequence if we see is it.
Is it possible to see the same BOM in
PAS-X?
Yeah.
Maybe we can take a look at it.
Yeah. Yeah. I think one of the pictures.
So I sent was the BOM
On that specific line, but but,
but we can check,
I mean we can go through the XML and then
we can check PAS-X as well.
Yeah, OK. OK. So let's park this.
We can keep continue and then we see the
Yeah, yeah.
same BOM there. Yeah.
Yeah. And we also have here,
we have multiple of the same positions
and these are line specific as well.
So depending on what line you have
registered the order for,
they will get sent down for line.
One or two
OK.
And I think those are all the views.
Yeah.
So we saw the material,
we saw material specific,
Should we should.
then we saw line specific and then now we
are looking at the BOM.
Yeah. And we we started with the batch.
Right.
The rush data itself.
Right.
Yeah.
I see that there are no recipes that are
shared between MOVE-X and PAS-X.
Maybe it's because of how the MBR is
managed there. So all the operation data.
So if there are phase in phases and
operations.
Are they available in MOVE-X or directly
only available in PAS-X?
So.
Uh, what do you mean free system?
So. So let's take an example I have.
When I'm just giving a very random
example. Now I have a production order,
it's going on some line and it has a
recipe around it will have.
Operations. Let's take an example.
Operation 10 will be like mixing right.
Operation 2 will be mixing plus grinding.
Whatever. Yeah.
And then operation 10 will be.
Coating. Sorry.
Operation 30 will be coating.
So in this case are these operations and
it's information kept in MOVE-X or it's
only part of PAS-X?
I think it's only part of PAS-X, right?
When you did report time for the
different.
Um.
For different stages before in MOVE-X,
but you don't really do that anymore.
I don't think maybe the assets are still
existing in MOVE-X,
OK.
but not really used in any way.
OK, no problem. Thank you. Yeah. Thanks.
So we will,
I I think.
we will take a look at this BOM and also
there you know the operations in PAS-X
later on once we move ahead.
Yeah.
OK,
so we took the XML here in the a column
and then we wrote down the different
categories.
The batch specific article specific type.
Uh line and BOM.
And then we try to match the the rows
like manufacturing order number,
the ordered quantity.
The dates and time and Stefan,
I don't know. And or Jorgen.
This is the exact time with the planning
so 1359.
This is the date when it's sent down.
To to because it it it probably changes
when you when you send it right.
So this is not planned time.
This is the sent date.
Yeah, it should be,
since since the one below is have the
exact same data.
Yeah, these are continuing with, yeah,
all the time.
But but this time is the this order was
originally planned 20250902.
And not 4 but it was sent down the 4th.
And this is the exact time that was,
it was planned.
So it kept the time for planning.
But it it's changed this to when it's
actually sent down,
Yeah.
so I'm and it was sent down like 11:00 AM
or something like that.
So I I don't know why it why it's built
like that, but that's what we found.
But shouldn't it be sent down at the same
time that it was planned?
I mean, we have a 2 dice.
No.
No. You have a plan. No,
you have a you have a.
You have a planned start that you just
fill out out to get them into the right
order in in the like the planning view.
Why this information is coming from where
batch the start date or the planned date?
Yeah, that's the. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Well,
but. But this. Yeah,
I'm not entirely sure if it's it's
changed.
Like in in the MOVE-X when you send it
down, it updates.
And this is like the latest update that
is done in.
In MOVE-X,
or if it's just the time it or date it's
sent down.
I think I think we already have a date
time in the order, right?
When we were looking at the date or the
order, there was a start date and time.
So I think this information is coming
from the order itself,
Yeah, yeah.
not not via the batch.
Batch is more about uh, you know,
the expiry date or the manufacturing date
when we have the you know the goods are
created or manufactured.
This is a system time,
probably when the order has been created
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's.
That's when it's sent down that date.
or.
And this time is when it's generated,
but yeah.
There could be also a possibility that
first it was a planned order and then it
So.
was formed after the PPDS process has
happened.
So it could be those 2 dates possibly.
Yeah, yeah.
But this remained the same,
but this changed.
This kind of data isn't that standard in
SAP or OneS4.
OK.
Yeah, it is standard. It's standard it.
It will come from the. It will come.
Yeah. OK.
So we don't need to waste time on this.
Yeah. So yeah.
We don't. Yeah, we don't.
We don't worry so much, correct.
Yeah, I feel like we maybe don't need to.
Maybe. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Let's see this one.
I'm a bit unsure about. Stefan works.
It's that workstation. Is that the plant?
I can. No I can.
I think it's it's.
Yeah, that, this,
that is only one we have a bit one big
I can explain.
Uh.
area for everything.
This is a fixed value.
OK.
Yeah. OK, so standard value.
Yeah.
So it's a standard value.
Currently I see that you your MOVE-X is
calling it 001.
That's your company code or a plant.
But within SAP from the logistic
perspective,
Hmm hmm.
we have something called as a company
code and a company could have company
code could have.
Multiple plants associated with it and
this is that code.
Hmm.
So for let's say for example Helsingborg
will be something SE01 as you will see it
in another STF systems and so on.
So that will come from SAP.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. And I think it's plant 01 in PAS-X.
But yes, this was.
This was also a related question I had
last week when we're discussing that you
know now that you are receiving the plant
as 001 in future. Once OneS4 comes,
it will become a 4 digit code which will
be let's say SE01,
HSB or HBG1 , something of that sort.
Will that impact PAS-X? Is there any?
Are there changes that are required?
Yes it will.
Yes.
So it would be good if you could send 001
as it's or zero one as it's received in
PAS-X because this area is also used in
PAS-X.
for the whole plant.
So I mean that is possibility to have 02
for example we don't use that we don't
have 01. So that is kind of a default.
So if we send down something else on 01,
Then PAS-X don't know what to do with it,
and we need to reconfigure.
It's possible of course,
but it would be good to have it.
OK.
And and there is and the effort to change
all of this is very high in PAS-X,
let's say just asking hypothetically.
The reason is that.
We need to know the effort,
so based on that we'll give a solution.
So for example, if it is,
let's say everything that is 001 now
needs to change to let's say HBG1 or SE01,
will it have a very high impact on your
system?
Possible we need to look into it.
It could be that we only need need to
OK.
change in some places,
but also that there might be older data
that is using it and then we.
Should not change it so but but.
But we need to look into it.
Hmm.
No, no problem, no problem.
I know we we have a.
Meeting in an hour, an hour for something,
and hopefully,
of course we have above is there,
maybe he can answer straight ahead on
that one.
OK, perfect.
So so Stefan only asking so that if the
effort is high,
we could recommend to keep it the same
and you know keep moving keep like a
cross mapping between 2 systems.
But let's also discuss you.
I would expect that you, you know,
if your team can also take a little bit
of a look at it and see the impact and
also the testing effort right,
because it's not only changing,
Hmm.
it also may require a very.
Uh, some kind of a testing effort on that.
So just kind of look at it in the high
level.
Yes.
OK. Thank you. Yeah, Max,
we can move ahead.
Yes,
this line is the status update as far as
like we could find. Yeah, batch number.
Yeah, that's pretty standard.
Can. Ohh that's? Yeah.
OK batch number and then we have these.
OK, we only have one of these.
OK. And we were a bit unsure but.
These are. Yeah, these are operations.
Yeah. This is what I was talking about.
Hmm.
The operations, right,
how the operations and phases correct.
The ERP positions.
Correct. So, within SAP,
you have like a BOM.
And then the BOM basically is attached to
something called as a recipe.
So BOM is what shows,
what are the components.
The recipe shows what are the components,
what is the,
let's say the production line associated
with it.
And what are the operations that are
going to happen on that?
Hmm.
So that's something called as a recipe,
right.
And the recipe manages a lot of that,
those parameters that you we were
discussing about.
But now since we are not sending the
recipe.
Or the BOM. We need to understand. OK,
how is the current system sending those
operations?
And that's what we are looking at,
but we still need to.
I would say architect that or solution
that within SAP so that the right data is
picked up.
Because we were a bit unsure about this
line because we we have these numbers
coming up later and those are linked to
the different basic operations with the
ERP position linked to them.
And this looks like an overview or
Yep.
something.
Uh, I'm not entirely sure,
so it's not filled in with any colour or
so.
OK, no problem.
So I will just mark it yellow here.
Not entirely sure about that one again
the time.
And date and then we come coming down to
the BOM.
And never we have the quantity,
the material number,
the unit of measurement.
And we have the BOM position.
So we're actually sending the BOM
position as well,
which as far as I know is not used in
PAS-X.
Uh.
And these code.
All all these are components right of the
of the semi finish or finished product.
Yeah, based on the order.
Yeah, the input.
These are the input materials, yes.
Yeah. OK.
So it just goes on for all the different
materials in the same way. Let's just see.
Yeah, yeah.
You are not using the the position of the
BOM component, but what? Yeah,
The ERP.
but what is the component here?
It's from the ERP position?
Or is it sending the PAS-X?
So this on these lines,
it's the BOM position,
the MOVE-X one and as far as I know we
don't really use it to any anything like
OK.
Yeah.
OK.
this row here.
OK 51,50,66. These are all PAS-X position,
No Sorry, MOVE-X position. OK, clear.
Yes, yes,
and all this data comes not that one,
Yeah.
but all this data comes in a another row
which are more detailed later.
OK. Yeah.
So PAS-X doesn't care about the MOVE-X
position at all.
Hmm.
It does care about the article number.
That is what it cares about.
Yeah.
To find the material.
Yeah, yeah.
OK.
Yep.
We have a other another meeting in one
minute, so we really need to drop out.
I don't need.
I don't know if you want to continue with
some of the.
Yeah, me and underneath to drop.
Meeting members.
If Max is there, if Max is available,
probably I we can spend it 5-10 minutes
I mean.
extra only if Max is available.
Yeah, yeah, I can. I can go on a bit.
I will.
Yeah. OK.
OK. So it's Kim doing this. OK. Yeah,
yeah, yeah, sure. Yeah. Right.
Yeah.
Sorry.
OK. Thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I don't know if you're gonna book a new
meeting, maybe in a few days. Yeah. Yeah.
OK. OK. Thank you.
Yeah, maybe a follow up. Yeah,
follow up surely. OK.
Thank you. OK, Max,
if we go little bit below now these are
of course the operations which you
mentioned that.
Yes.
This doesn't matter in MOVE-X, right?
Sorry.
Ohh ohh these.
I mean it it does because because when
it's not set up properly it doesn't work
so they they the I don't see the sum of
OK.
the VOR numbers that we had in in the
MOVE-X.
We had 7 but I don't see the number here.
I only see that when you look at the
final position of the ERP related basic
operations, you have 7.
Correct.
So.
I I guess that needs to match for it to
be able to to send the data.
But I'm not entirely sure why.
OK.
It is basically the operation data and
I'm assuming let's go below little bit
below because until here it's pretty
standard.
What is different is this one below right
that?
This one.
No, line 277. This is where.
Ohh yeah.
Right.
This is where we are sending all the GMBR
related parameters.
Yeah, yeah, we started article specific.
Yeah, once. Yeah.
Correct.
Now are you sending each and every
Operation one more time here.
Can you confirm that so?
Operation you mean this one?
No. If you go down now, you had,
let's say 7 operations,
correct and what you're trying to do is
you're trying basically not to you,
but at least the system what it is trying
to do is now it's trying to send all the
information.
That is collected at the parameter level.
So here we saw these one right, the Max,
Hmm.
and these were your material specific
parameters.
Yeah, yeah.
Correct.
So we know that some of these are article
and I think you have rightly mapped them.
Let's go a little bit below what are the
other.
Yeah.
And this one just jumped in in the middle
here with the target material and target
quantity.
This is very order specific, right?
This is very order order.
Yeah, yeah.
OK.
And then it continued a bit with the
article specific.
OK, let's go.
And then we had the article type.
But then we get the line specific.
Can we look at the line specific ones,
line specific ones, so you're,
That all the.
Yeah, sure. Just a second.
am I going to see B0067 until 7 or there
are more?
There are probably more 8 or 9,
let's say 10. 09,
so there are there are basic operations
that are not linked to an ERP position.
So that's why they're not named in this
101,102.
OK.
I think we have a a couple name,
a couple of rooms that are not linked.
OK.
OK, let's let's scroll a little bit down.
So BOM is, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And and just this is 009.
So just having the connection to the 009
gives you this parameter. It's a,
it's a yeah, Boolean.
It's true if it's an active product and
and you get the material number,
you get the position and you get the
quantity. But.
The the number here.
You don't get it translated to just 9.
It still says 5.
It still says the the BOM position.
So this is what is used for the.
And.
The ERP position like these,
these are parameters.
OK. And and the BOM.
So let's look at this one. Yeah,
the line 605.
Line 605.
Uh, yes.
Yeah.
So this is a BOM position and this is
Yeah.
basically BOM 009.
POS is the ERP position and which is the
5 which is 5 this PAS-X?
No 9 is PAS-X.
9 is PAS-X, 5 is MOVE-X. OK, OK clear now.
Now it's kind of clear.
Yes, yeah, 5 is MOVE-X, yeah.
I understand that it's basically trying
to.
Yeah. So yeah.
So from that 9 that is set up in PXS 130,
it generates that this boolean parameter
is true when it's in the BOM,
it generates the
The material number in that specific row
and it has the number and the yeah.
And also the BOM and and then the
quantity or quantity.
OK.
So it doesn't say we don't really find
these in in MOVE-X.
And not anywhere where we usually work
anyway so.
This is this is what I could find in that
table what was shared with me. I will.
I will share that screen as well but
these are coming from those PXOPAR table.
Hmm.
Yeah. Yeah. OK.
So what I see in PXOPAR table is
basically the entire structure and that's
why you must have seen my messages.
Please share me the screenshots and I
will let you know.
Maybe we can just Scroll down a little
bit, look at other parameters that are.
Yep.
I think it's basically the BOM,
then rest of the message, yeah.
OK.
OK, yeah, this is fine.
What I did not understand properly or was
the was the line specific.
Can you go to the line specific once?
Yeah. Then take the up here.
Yeah. Stop. Stop. Yeah.
So what does this indicate?
Can you explain me one example?
Yeah. Yeah, so,
so this this is a container type and it's
it's a parameterized to decide which
equipment or container to use.
So on line one they will use these.
For some reason,
there's a line one as well that is
dedicated, but it is line 2, line 2,
line 2 and then you have the production
units.
Uh,
and with the code to those specific
computers or yeah. So,
we use the same GMBR for line 1 and line
2 and send this line specific data like
this
Hmm.
So So what I'm seeing is mostly your
entire PAS-X structure is getting created
through this parameters.
Yes. Yeah.
Right.
And that is like the main driver for the
PAS-X system.
Yeah. So in PAS-X, we have the GMBR,
the generic master batch record,
and then we combine it with our PVL
parameter value list and then the PVL
OK.
gets populated with all of.
These values and that creates the unique
master batch record.
OK, yeah,
this this now as a as a technique,
it's understood we still need to probably
work a little bit on.
Yeah.
What are the exact values you know for?
A GMBR. How do they influence?
Because that's something I'm trying to
Hmm.
find out. OK, Max,
can we do you have anything else on this
front or we go now to the interface or we
go to the PAS-X to see the same?
Yeah,
we can go to PAS-X kind of say can login.
I.
In production.
It's gonna log in here as well.
So let's see what's the order.
So I'm.
I mean, I guess I can show.
Because this this is the order.
But it's in the in this room,
so maybe I should show the GMBR because
OK.
you need to see the like the structure.
We have several rooms.
Correct.
Yeah, so,
so this is the structure and everyone of
these are the basic operations.
Umm.
And you can see the ERP position here.
So it has the 101.
Next, room 102 etcetera.
And we set up all the input materials
like this.
So you see the ERP position here,
it's BOM 005 plus.
Then you have the active parameter,
the material number and the target.
OK.
And then each one of these have their own
workstations or computers,
so it's hard to get like an overview of
the of the whole order in the production
environment because I cannot.
You know, bring every everyone of those.
OK, I I I was expecting that OK,
if I open an order I would see what are
the operations associated with it.
So that was.
Yeah, I mean we could, yeah,
we could like see an overview,
I guess in here.
See the batch number again.
So this is the order in.
Let's see if I right click it,
it will get all the like the operations
all the rooms in in one list and when I
click them you can see all the the.
Input materials and and the target
materials etcetera.
So here, here you see the.
The positions of the materials.
The names and the in the targets,
etcetera.
But this is the BOM, correct?
Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The actual parameters is.
Where can I? Where can I see it?
Like a recipe? For example,
if I want to see.
Yeah.
Let's see.
And we combine our GMBR with PVL and it
creates a PMBR.
And that is the template that is used.
So this one.
Is that PMBR like you have like a visual
representation of that one?
Umm.
I guess that it's the most official is
like the the GMBR,
which we were in like to see all the yeah.
And these are the parameter list.
OK.
So here you have the.
OK.
All the parameters.
Undecided. Then you have the value.
And and and the value here is just it's
standard values in in PAS-X which will be
overrided by MOVE-X.
MOVE-X
So. So these will all be override.
This is just standard values that are put
in.
In in this example,
how many operations are there?
What do you mean exactly by operations
like like steps in the production?
So so for example, yeah correct.
So for example when I.
When I looked at some of your data,
that's the production order I had pasted
when I looked at it, it showed me OK,
there are there is operation 20 which is
Hmm.
your main manufacturing phase.
Mm-hmm.
And so let me share my screen. Yeah,
I'll just give an example of what was the
information I was looking for to
basically looked at your PXOPAR.
This is how the list was getting
extracted from the PVL and I tried to
build it so I could build it and I could
see something like this like face
sequence material when I put it together.
And this was for that particular material
231251 and I was trying to understand, OK,
Hmm.
how is this getting built,
it's more or less how you're telling me
it's getting built like this but?
Once it is built,
I wanted to show I wanted to check if
what I was building and what displayed in
the in your PAS-X is matching.
OK.
So and that was my idea that, you know,
if I get a screenshot because within SAP
for example there is something called as
a recipe, I could, you know,
go to the recipe,
open that recipe and the planning version
of that.
And I could see,
OK what are the operations that really
are affecting this one?
OK. OK. Yeah.
Because so for for these manufacturing
orders,
we have different preparation steps where
we weigh and measure the input materials,
so for.
Yeah.
Parallel steps where we use multiple
input materials in the same step.
But these are all in in different rooms
and and are prepared basically
Got it.
simultaneously.
Simultaneously clear, clear.
Yeah.
All these 4 need - this is the unique
room for line 2 as well so this is not
active on line 1,
2 parameter here and the ERP position.
Good.
Yes, it's still one worked order,
but then it's broken down into shop floor
orders for each room.
Yeah. Yeah, exactly.
Correct, right, right it.
It is even more detailed than what you
would receive from SAP.
It's splitted more.
Yeah, yeah.
You know more operational execution way.
Yeah. No, it makes sense.
Yeah, yeah.
I have one question.
Ohh, while we're talking,
Jorgen is not there,
but are the other sides using similar
technique like for example?
Are you aware if Pomezia is using GMBR>
I know they are using GMBR but are they
using GMBR with parameters?
Like this, like how you guys are and are.
Do you have any idea about other sites?
If there are,
they are also using the planning variable,
the planning parameters.
Hmm.
As far as I know,
we're pretty far ahead when it when it
comes to these things. Most companies.
What I've heard is that they only use
straight master batch record like
finished MBRs and not GMBRs to.
Correct, correct.
So I think we're quite a bit ahead when
it comes to those things and and we we
really need it as well as we have like
over 800 SKUs. So we have a lot of.
Yeah,
I think the complexity mandates that we
have these and we have the most complex
setup and maintenance on this as well.
And today we have.
28 PMBRs that are effective and that
PMBRs, we got 65 of them effective.
Yeah, yeah, I think it's 28.
OK.
And and this effectively takes care of
all the SKUs?
Yeah.
Yes.
OK,
but is pomezia using it in the similar
fashion or let's say Val de Reuil using
it in the similar fashion?
I am unsure,
but as I said the the the what I've heard
is that the the sites that are using
PAS-X are basically only using MBRs so
not sending down
Parameters at all
From the ERP.
Yeah, because yes,
because when I looked at some of the
documentation for Pomezia,
I did not find these parameters there and
Yeah, yeah.
that's why we are having the next call
later on.
To understand,
you know if Pomezia  did something
Yeah.
similar and so on,
because this is this is a good concept of
like making everything generic,
less maintenance however.
We also need to make sure the data is
passed in in this manner to the to the
PAS-X system.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I believe that the process,
it's not for the whole production in
OK.
maybe this in one of the sites.
But I think value they don't have it.
Everywhere and also the process is not as
complex or they're only using some part
of the capabilities while we have it
everywhere and everything is covered so.
So we have we need to have an order
approach.
I cannot say if other sites are using
something similar approach like for
Washington. Maybe I don't know.
Again this would be a question.
For the, it was Pablo, the main MES guy.
OK.
So we can ask him that.
Yeah. So, Stefan,
I think you are there in the next call,
right? We could discuss this topic.
Yes. Yeah, we can talk with uh,
Oscar then I don't have any more
Up.
information with the complexity,
but I think it is like that.
OK.
And we and you will be able to explain it
much better than me to them?
Yeah. And also like Marcus,
he probably knows a bit about it as well,
At least the parameter, yeah.
so I think.
OK. OK then perfect, Max. Max,
would you send us that XML so I can just
compare it with our recording.
Yeah, yes, yes. I'll send it.
And and that was the actual interface
sent by the system, correct the XML.
Uh, yes,
but not for the exact order we checked
now, but but the same product. Ohh yeah.
Ohh OK can you?
Mostly give probably give me also the
extract for the same product what we
discussed in our call. It's easy.
Yeah. Yeah. No, no, no. It was this,
the same product,
the same article number as well.
But the batch number differed.
OK.
So it's it's, I mean, yeah.
Only the production order was different.
Doesn't matter. Yeah. OK. OK.
Yeah, yeah, exactly. Yeah.
Thank you guys.
It was very helpful and I'll set up a
follow up.
Let me and my team look at this from the
documentation and after today's call,
I will get back.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much. Bye.
Right. Thank you. OK, bye bye.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Thank you. Bye.